<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Art into Science</title><link>https://artintoscience.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Art into Science</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artintoscience.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ACoD is back!</title><link>https://artintoscience.com/posts/hello/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://artintoscience.com/posts/hello/</guid><description>We are thrilled to announce the return of the Art into Science conference (ACoD)! After an impactful previous season, we are back to continue our mission of pushing the art of security into a recognized professional discipline. The conference will be held in Washington D.C. from October 25 to 27, 2023.
We&amp;rsquo;ve crafted ACoD with two key goals in mind:
Push the Art to a Science: We aim to foster a space where security methodologies are shared systematically and consistently, turning our diverse collection of professionals into a unified professional discipline.</description><content>&lt;p>We are thrilled to announce the return of the Art into Science conference (ACoD)! After an impactful previous season, we are back to continue our mission of pushing the art of security into a recognized professional discipline. The conference will be held in Washington D.C. from October 25 to 27, 2023.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ve crafted ACoD with two key goals in mind:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Push the Art to a Science: We aim to foster a space where security methodologies are shared systematically and consistently, turning our diverse collection of professionals into a unified professional discipline. We discuss, model, and advance security concepts to facilitate this evolution.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Glorify the Defense: While many conferences focus on attack strategies, ACoD chooses to spotlight the defenders. We welcome operational talks on defense, offering attendees actionable tools, techniques, and ideas to apply in their own environments.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>ACoD is a working conference, with tracks that explore various investigations, case studies, and defense tools on the operations side, while philosophically pushing the boundaries of security science on the other.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We also understand the value of connections formed during such events. Hence, we&amp;rsquo;ve built opportunities for networking, group discussions, and collaborations into our agenda. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an introvert or an extrovert, you will find opportunities to connect with others and learn how we can help each other advance in our field.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Call for Papers (CFP) opens on July 1 and closes on August 18, 2023. We strongly encourage, and look forward to submissions from professionals of all backgrounds. Please consider contributing your unique perspective and experiences to our community.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Information about ticketing will be available soon.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Not sure if Art into Science is for you? Take a peek at our &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBZP-ZKcqgN4xjj6MfIgbVA">Youtube channel&lt;/a> to view presentations from our previous conference or follow us on Twitter to stay updated with the latest news from ACoD.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Mark your calendars and get ready to push the boundaries of security science. We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see you at the Art into Science conference!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Stay tuned for more updates!&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>