<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Art into Science</title><link>https://artintoscience.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Art into Science</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://artintoscience.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Art Into Science: A Conference on Defense</title><link>https://artintoscience.com/posts/hello/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://artintoscience.com/posts/hello/</guid><description>Art Into Science: A Conference on Defense
October 25-26, 2023
Appian HQ in Tysons Corner, VA | 7950 Jones Branch Dr, McLean, VA 22102
ACoD is a working conference, with tracks that explore various investigations, case studies, and defense tools on the operations side, while philosophically pushing the boundaries of security science on the other. We’ve crafted ACoD with two key goals in mind:
Push the Art to a Science: We aim to foster a space where security methodologies are shared systematically and consistently, turning our diverse collection of professionals into a unified professional discipline.</description><content>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Art Into Science: A Conference on Defense&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>October 25-26, 2023&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Appian HQ in Tysons Corner, VA | &lt;a href="https://goo.gl/maps/RthWv3UEvdH5Gwx9A">7950 Jones Branch Dr, McLean, VA 22102&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ACoD is a working conference, with tracks that explore various investigations, case studies, and defense tools on the operations side, while philosophically pushing the boundaries of security science on the other. We’ve crafted ACoD with two key goals in mind:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Push the Art to a Science: We aim to foster a space where security methodologies are shared systematically and consistently, turning our diverse collection of professionals into a unified professional discipline. We discuss, model, and advance security concepts to facilitate this evolution.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Glorify the Defense: While many conferences focus on attack strategies, ACoD chooses to spotlight the defenders. We welcome operational talks on defense, offering attendees actionable tools, techniques, and ideas to apply in their own environments.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>Not sure if Art into Science is for you? Take a peek at our &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@aconferencefordefense-acod8650">Youtube channel&lt;/a> to view presentations from our previous conference.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ready to join us? A limited number of tickets are still available. Secure your spot today!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We can’t wait to see you at the Art into Science conference. Visit our &lt;a href="https://artintoscience.com/schedule/">Schedule and Venue&lt;/a> page for more information about travel and the daily schedule for the conference.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/art-into-science-a-conference-on-defense-tickets-656839754387">Get your tickets here!&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ACoD is still free but space is limited. Sign up to secure your spot!&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>